♪ ♪
♪ WICKED OR WEAKNESS, ♪
♪ YOU GOTTA SEE THIS,
WAAAAAY (YEAH, YEAH!) ♪
♪ AYE, I REMEMBER
SYRUP SANDWICHES AND
CRIME ALLOWANCES ♪
♪ FINESSE A NIGGA WIT
SUM COUNTERFEITS ♪
♪ BUT NOW I'M COUNTIN THIS ♪
♪ PARMESAN WHERE MY
ACCOUNTANT LIVES IN
FACT I'M DOWN AT THIS ♪
♪ DUSSE WIT MY BOO
BAE, TASTES LIKE KOOL
AID FOR THE ANALYSTS ♪
♪ GIRL, I CAN BUY YOUR ASS
THE WORLD WIT MY PAYSTUB ♪
♪ OOH THAT PUSSY GOOD, WON'T
YOU SIT IT ON MY TASTE BLOODS ♪
♪ I GET WAY TOO PETTY ONCE
YOU LET ME DO THE EXTRAS ♪
♪ PULL UP ON YOUR
BLOCK, THEN BREAK IT
DOWN WE PLAYIN TETRIS ♪
♪ A.M. TO THE P.M.,
P.M. TO THE A.M. FUNK ♪
♪ PISS OUT YOUR PER DIEM
YOU JUS GOTTA HATE EM, FUNK ♪
♪ IF I QUIT YOUR BM I STILL
RIDE MERCEDES, FUNK ♪
♪ IF I QUIT THIS SEASON I
STILL BE THE GREATEST, FUNK ♪
♪ MY LEFT STROKE
JUST WENT VIRAL ♪
♪ RIGHT STROKE PUT
LIL BABY IN A SPIRAL ♪
♪ SOPRANO C, WE LIKE TO
KEEP IT ON A HIGH NOTE ♪
♪ IT'S LEVELS TO IT, YOU AND
I KNOW...BITCH BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH) SIT DOWN, ♪
♪ (HOL' UP LIL BITCH, HOL'
UP, LIL BITCH) BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH) SIT DOWN
(SIT DOWN HOL' UP LIL BITCH) ♪
♪ BE HUMBLE (BITCH) ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP, HOL' UP,
HOL' UP) BITCH SIT DOWN ♪
♪ LIL BITCH (HOL' UP LIL
BITCH) BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH) SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP, HOL'
UP, HOL' UP) BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP, HOL' UP,
HOL' UP LIL BITCH) SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (HOL' UP LIL BITCH)
BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH) SIT DOWN
(HOL' UP SIT DOWN LIL BITCH) ♪
♪ (SIT DOWN LIL BITCH)
BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP, HOL'
UP, HOL' UP LIL BITCH)
BITCH, SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (HOL' UP LIL BITCH)
BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH)
SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP,
HOL' UP, HOL' UP) ♪
♪ WHO DAT NIGGA THINKIN THAT HE
FRONTIN ON MAN MAN (MAN MAN) ♪
♪ GET THE FUCK OFF MY STAGE,
I'M THE SANDMAN (SANDMAN) ♪
♪ GET THE FUCK OFF MY
DICK, THAT AINT' RIGHT ♪
♪ I MAKE A PLAY FUCKING
UP YOUR WHOLE LIFE ♪
♪ IM SO FUCKEN SICK AND
TIRED OF THE PHOTOSHOP ♪
♪ SHOW ME SOMETHING NATURAL
LIKE AFRO ON RICHARD PRYOR ♪
♪ SHOW ME SOMETHING
NATURAL LIKE ASS WIT
SOME STRETCHMARKS ♪
♪ STILL WILL TAKE YOU DOWN
RIGHT ON YOUR MOMMA'S
COUCH IN POLO SOCKS AYE ♪
♪ THIS SHIT WAY
TOO CRAZY AYE ♪
♪ YOU DO NOT AMAZE ME AYE ♪
♪ I BLEW COOL FROM AC AYE ♪
♪ OBAMA JUST PAGED ME AYE ♪
♪ I DON'T FABRICATE IT AYE ♪
♪ MOST OF YALL BE FAKIN AYE ♪
♪ I STAY MODEST BOUT IT AYE ♪
♪ SHE ELABORATE IT AYE ♪
♪ THIS THAT GREY POUPON,
THAT EVIAN, THAT TED TALK AYE ♪
♪ WATCH MY SOUL SPEAK,
YOU LET THE MEDS TALK AYE ♪
♪ IF I KILL A NIGGA IT WON'T
BE THE ALCOHOL AYE ♪
♪ I'M THE REALEST NIGGA
AFTER ALL BITCH BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH) SIT DOWN, ♪
♪ (HOL' UP LIL BITCH, HOL' UP,
LIL BITCH) BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH) SIT DOWN
(SIT DOWN HOL' UP LIL BITCH) ♪
♪ BE HUMBLE (BITCH) ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP, HOL' UP,
HOL' UP) BITCH SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (LIL BITCH) (HOL' UP
LIL BITCH) BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH) SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP, HOL'
UP, HOL' UP) BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP, HOL' UP,
HOL' UP LIL BITCH) SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (HOL' UP LIL
BITCH) BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH) SIT DOWN
(HOL' UP SIT DOWN LIL BITCH) ♪
♪ (SIT DOWN LIL BITCH)
BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP,
HOL' UP, HOL' UP LIL
BITCH) BITCH, SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (HOL' UP LIL BITCH)
BE HUMBLE ♪
♪ (HOL' UP BITCH)
SIT DOWN ♪
♪ (HOL' UP, HOL' UP,
HOL' UP, HOL' UP) ♪
♪ ♪